LEICESTERSHIRE I-ORG O
West I-MISC I-LOC
Indian I-MISC I-LOC
Kent I-ORG I-PER
Such I-PER O
the O I-LOC
Derbyshire I-ORG I-PER
Kent I-ORG I-PER
ex-England I-MISC O
Leicester I-LOC O
Kent I-ORG I-PER
Moody I-PER I-ORG
ASHES I-MISC O
Ashes I-MISC I-ORG
Test I-ORG O
and I-ORG O
Tour O I-MISC
Arrive O I-PER
Duke I-ORG I-PER
of I-ORG O
Norfolk I-ORG I-LOC
's I-ORG O
XI I-ORG O
Derbyshire I-ORG I-PER
Manchester I-LOC I-ORG
Fourth O I-ORG
Kent I-ORG I-PER
ENGLAND I-LOC O
Dinamo I-ORG I-PER
ROTOR I-ORG O
LOCKED O I-ORG
VOLGOGRAD I-LOC O
Rotor I-ORG O
Rotor I-ORG O
Volgograd I-LOC I-ORG
ROBERTO I-PER O
DURAN I-PER I-ORG
FIGHTS O I-ORG
THE O I-ORG
SANDS O I-ORG
Panamanian I-MISC O
" I-PER O
Hands I-PER O
of I-PER O
Stone I-PER I-LOC
" I-PER O
Duran I-PER O
" O I-ORG
Return I-MISC I-ORG
of I-MISC O
the I-MISC O
Panamanian I-MISC O
Association I-ORG O
President O I-ORG
Ramon I-PER I-ORG
Manzanares I-PER I-ORG
" I-PER O
" I-PER O
Panamanian I-MISC O
Hong I-MISC I-LOC
Kong I-MISC I-LOC
Open I-MISC I-LOC
Suwan I-ORG O
PROFESSIONAL O I-MISC
Lotte I-ORG I-PER
Lotte I-ORG I-PER
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
YORK I-ORG I-LOC
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
YORK I-ORG I-LOC
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
YORK I-ORG I-LOC
TARANGO I-PER O
SPRING O I-PER
TWIN O I-ORG
UPSETS O I-ORG
Washington I-PER I-LOC
Stadium O I-LOC
Washington I-PER I-LOC
Washington I-PER I-LOC
Washington I-PER I-LOC
Washington I-PER I-LOC
Texan I-MISC O
Washington I-PER I-LOC
Washington I-PER I-LOC
Tarango I-PER O
Rios I-PER I-MISC
AMERICAN I-MISC I-ORG
FOOTBALL-RANDALL I-MISC I-ORG
CUNNINGHAM I-PER I-ORG
RETIRES O I-ORG
Football I-ORG I-MISC
League I-ORG I-MISC
Pro I-MISC O
Bowl I-MISC O
Eagles I-ORG I-MISC
Philadelphia I-ORG I-LOC
NFL I-ORG I-MISC
Eagles I-ORG I-MISC
Philadelphia I-LOC O
GREATER I-MISC I-LOC
MILWAUKEE I-MISC I-LOC
OPEN I-MISC I-LOC
MILWAUKEE I-LOC I-ORG
Greater I-MISC O
Brown I-LOC I-PER
Deer I-LOC I-ORG
Park I-LOC I-ORG
Golf I-LOC I-ORG
Course I-LOC O
Tiger I-PER I-ORG
Woods I-PER I-ORG
WOODS I-PER I-ORG
MAKES O I-ORG
PRO O I-ORG
DEBUT O I-ORG
MILWAUKEE I-LOC I-ORG
Greater I-MISC O
Tiger I-PER I-ORG
Woods I-PER I-ORG
Woods I-PER I-LOC
Wednesday O I-PER
victories O I-MISC
Woods I-PER O
EXCUSE O I-ORG
FORMER O I-MISC
post-Games I-MISC O
Berlin I-MISC I-LOC
STANDARD I-ORG O
Bisconti I-PER O
EDWARDS I-PER O
MONTE I-LOC O
CARLO I-LOC O
Solidarity I-MISC I-ORG
Meeting I-MISC I-ORG
for I-MISC O
Sarajevo I-MISC I-LOC
Kosevo I-LOC O
Atlanta I-MISC B-MISC
Final I-MISC O
BARATELLI I-PER O
NICE I-ORG I-LOC
MILAN I-ORG I-PER
ATALANTA I-ORG O
serie I-MISC O
A I-MISC O
dello I-ORG O
Atalanta I-ORG I-PER
Bergamo-based I-MISC O
Atalanta I-ORG I-PER
ex-Milan I-MISC O
Torino I-ORG I-LOC
U. I-PER I-ORG
Chandana I-PER I-ORG
Next O I-MISC
Series O I-MISC
Upul I-PER O
COMELF I-ORG O
Comelf I-ORG O
Comelf I-ORG O
Comelf I-ORG O
Transylvanian I-MISC I-LOC
Comelf I-ORG I-PER
POLISH I-MISC I-ORG
OPERATION O I-LOC
M3 O I-LOC
ST. I-LOC I-ORG
LOUIS I-LOC I-ORG
St. I-LOC I-ORG
Petersburg I-LOC O
Jones I-ORG I-MISC
Jones I-ORG I-LOC
Daniels I-ORG I-PER
Pharmaceuticals I-ORG I-PER
Levoxyl I-MISC O
New I-ORG I-LOC
York I-ORG I-LOC
Energy I-ORG I-LOC
Desk I-ORG I-LOC
NAPM I-ORG I-LOC
August O I-ORG
Chicago I-LOC I-ORG
Eurodollar I-MISC O
Eurodollar I-MISC O
Eurodollars I-MISC O
U.S. I-LOC I-MISC
T-bonds O I-ORG
Federal I-ORG I-MISC
Open I-ORG I-MISC
Market I-ORG I-MISC
Committee I-ORG I-MISC
CNBC I-ORG O
Jackson I-MISC I-PER
Hole I-MISC I-PER
symposium I-MISC O
FOMC I-ORG O
Eurodollars I-MISC I-PER
Douglas I-ORG I-PER
& I-ORG O
Lomason I-ORG O
FARMINGTON I-LOC I-ORG
HILLS I-LOC I-ORG
Douglas I-ORG I-PER
& I-ORG O
Magna I-ORG I-PER
Douglas I-ORG I-PER
& I-ORG O
Lomason I-ORG I-PER
Markham I-ORG I-PER
Ontario-based I-MISC O
Magna I-ORG I-PER
Johnson I-ORG I-PER
Controls I-ORG I-PER
Inc I-ORG I-PER
Lear I-ORG I-PER
Corp I-ORG I-PER
Douglas I-ORG I-PER
& I-ORG O
Lomason I-ORG I-PER
Douglas I-ORG I-PER
& I-ORG O
Lomason I-ORG I-PER
Magna I-ORG I-PER
Douglas I-ORG I-PER
& I-ORG O
Lomason I-ORG I-PER
Schroder I-ORG I-PER
Wertheim I-ORG I-PER
& I-ORG O
Magna I-ORG I-PER
Magna I-ORG I-PER
Magna I-ORG I-PER
Johnson I-ORG I-PER
Controls I-ORG I-PER
Lear I-ORG I-LOC
Thursday O I-LOC
GERMANY I-LOC O
Bunds O I-MISC
and I-ORG O
U.S. I-ORG I-LOC
Treasuries I-ORG O
Chicago I-MISC I-ORG
PMI I-MISC I-ORG
PMI O I-ORG
MATIF O I-ORG
UNITED I-LOC I-ORG
STATES I-LOC I-ORG
Chicago I-ORG I-LOC
Purchasing I-ORG O
September O I-ORG
Goverment I-MISC I-ORG
Bonds I-MISC I-ORG
EUROBONDS I-MISC O
U.S. I-LOC I-ORG
Labour I-MISC I-ORG
Day I-MISC I-ORG
NSW I-ORG O
DNIB I-ORG O
Kansai I-ORG I-PER
Electric I-ORG I-PER
Power I-ORG I-PER
Boxing-Bruno I-MISC O
World I-ORG O
WBC I-ORG I-LOC
the O I-ORG
McCarthy I-PER I-ORG
Birmingham I-ORG I-LOC
Given I-PER O
Little O I-PER
Uyo I-LOC I-PER
Driefontein I-ORG O
Gold I-ORG O
of I-ORG O
South I-ORG I-LOC
Africa I-ORG I-LOC
Ltd I-ORG I-LOC
Driefontein I-ORG O
and I-ORG O
' I-ORG O
Paramilitary O I-MISC
Chechnya I-LOC I-PER
Chechen I-LOC I-MISC
Republic I-LOC I-MISC
Aerodrom I-LOC I-ORG
Beograd I-LOC I-ORG
Lukashenko I-PER O
Tajik I-MISC O
Tajik I-MISC O
Pamir I-LOC I-MISC
Tavildara I-LOC I-PER
Tavildara I-LOC I-MISC
Layron I-LOC O
Tavildara I-LOC I-PER
Islamic I-MISC I-LOC
United I-MISC I-LOC
Nations-sponsored I-MISC O
Tavildara I-LOC I-PER
Tajik I-MISC O
Federal I-LOC I-ORG
Republic I-LOC I-ORG
of I-LOC O
Poles I-MISC O
Yastrzhembsky I-PER O
Barvikha I-LOC O
Moscow I-LOC O
Lavrentyeva I-PER O
France-registered I-MISC O
BSE I-ORG I-MISC
GDRs O I-LOC
IAS O I-LOC
GDRs O I-ORG
Petofi I-ORG I-LOC
Petofi I-ORG O
Petofi I-ORG I-LOC
Petofi I-ORG O
Petofi I-ORG I-LOC
Kecskemet I-LOC I-PER
Petofi I-ORG I-LOC
Petofi I-ORG I-LOC
Casa I-LOC I-MISC
de I-LOC O
Narino I-LOC I-MISC
New I-ORG I-LOC
Liberty I-ORG I-LOC
T3 I-LOC I-MISC
KNP I-ORG I-MISC
Gold O I-LOC
Mishi I-PER I-ORG
Saran I-PER I-ORG
Southeast I-MISC I-ORG
Asian I-MISC I-ORG
London I-LOC O
Easier O I-MISC
Comex O I-MISC
Eltahawy I-PER O
Libyans I-MISC I-ORG
Green O I-PER
Pan I-ORG O
Am I-ORG I-MISC
Green I-LOC I-PER
Square I-LOC I-PER
Jebel I-LOC I-MISC
al-Akhdar I-LOC O
Gaddafi I-PER O
For O I-ORG
Wall I-LOC I-ORG
Street I-LOC I-ORG
Whitewater I-LOC I-ORG
Clintons I-PER I-ORG
& I-ORG O
Brisk O I-ORG
Barnett I-ORG I-PER
FOMC I-ORG O
CNBC I-ORG O
Governor O I-ORG
Lawrence I-PER I-ORG
Lindsey I-PER I-ORG
of I-ORG O
Michigan I-ORG I-LOC
U.S. I-ORG I-LOC
Mexican I-MISC O
Northern O I-ORG
Northeastern O I-LOC
California I-LOC I-ORG
U.S. I-LOC I-MISC
World I-ORG I-MISC
Trade I-ORG I-MISC
U.S. I-LOC I-MISC
California I-LOC I-ORG
Drazek I-PER I-ORG
Chicago I-LOC I-ORG
Cardinal O I-ORG
Joseph I-PER I-ORG
Bernardin I-PER I-ORG
U.S. I-LOC I-MISC
Cincinnati I-LOC I-ORG
Boatmen I-ORG I-PER
's I-ORG O
Boatmen I-ORG I-LOC
's I-ORG O
NationsBank I-ORG O
Edward I-ORG I-PER
D. I-ORG I-PER
Jones I-ORG I-PER
& I-ORG O
or O I-ORG
St. I-MISC I-ORG
Louis-based I-MISC O
Boatmen I-ORG O
's I-ORG O
Kansas I-LOC I-ORG
City I-LOC I-ORG
Mo.-based I-MISC I-ORG
Mercantile I-ORG O
, O I-ORG
Roosevelt I-ORG I-PER
. O I-ORG
Louis I-MISC I-PER
and O I-ORG
Minneapolis-based I-MISC O
Ohio-based I-MISC O
KeyCorp I-ORG I-PER
Norwest I-ORG I-PER
One I-ORG O
KeyCorp I-ORG I-PER
Boatmen I-ORG I-PER
's I-ORG O
Boatmen I-ORG O
's I-ORG O
NationsBank I-ORG I-PER
Boatmen I-ORG O
's I-ORG O
Boatmen I-ORG O
's I-ORG O
NationsBank I-ORG I-LOC
Boatmen I-ORG O
's I-ORG O
NationsBank I-ORG I-PER
& I-ORG O
Nation I-ORG O
of I-ORG O
Islam I-ORG I-MISC
Million I-MISC I-PER
Man I-MISC I-PER
March I-MISC O
Pan I-MISC I-LOC
Am I-MISC O
flight I-MISC O
103 I-MISC O
Lockerbie I-LOC I-PER
Mediterranean I-MISC O
Clinton I-PER I-MISC
on I-ORG O
Presidential I-ORG O
Debates I-ORG O
League I-ORG I-MISC
of I-ORG O
Women I-ORG I-MISC
Voters I-ORG I-MISC
Titanic I-MISC O
RMS I-MISC I-ORG
Titanic I-MISC I-ORG
Titanic I-MISC I-ORG
Reagan I-ORG I-PER
Communications I-ORG I-PER
Titanic I-MISC O
Jewish I-MISC I-ORG
West I-LOC I-ORG
Bank I-LOC I-ORG
Foreign I-ORG O
Bonn I-LOC I-PER
German-Israeli I-MISC O
German I-MISC I-PER
Saint-Bernard I-LOC I-MISC
de I-LOC O
Christian I-PER I-MISC
Blanc I-PER I-MISC
GRONINGEN I-LOC I-ORG
Groningen I-LOC I-ORG
Hindustan I-ORG I-PER
Ready O I-ORG
Hindustan I-ORG O
Aluminium O I-ORG
Bond I-ORG O
Traders I-ORG O
' I-ORG O
Association I-ORG O
Aw O I-ORG
Data O I-MISC
IPO O I-ORG
Homegate I-ORG I-MISC
Hospitality I-ORG I-MISC
Inc I-ORG I-MISC
al-Gama'a I-ORG O
al-Islamiya I-ORG O
Islamic I-ORG I-LOC
Group I-ORG I-LOC
al-Saadani I-PER O
Al-Akhbar I-ORG I-MISC
Gama'a I-MISC I-LOC
AL-RAM I-LOC I-PER
al-Aqsa I-LOC O
Jamil I-PER O
Hebrew I-MISC I-LOC
al-Aqsa I-LOC O
al-Aqsa I-LOC O
al-Ram I-LOC O
Qalandia I-LOC I-MISC
, O I-ORG
Mich I-LOC I-ORG
Time O I-MISC
ST O I-ORG
MI I-LOC O
Detroit I-LOC I-ORG
Bodman I-ORG I-PER
, I-ORG O
& I-ORG O
Dahling I-ORG I-PER
Detroit I-LOC I-ORG
First I-ORG O
of I-ORG O
Michigan I-ORG I-LOC
Corp. I-ORG I-LOC
Department O I-ORG
U.S. I-LOC I-MISC
That O I-PER
Commerce O I-ORG
Markets O I-PER
Overnight O I-PER
NY I-MISC O
Nikkei I-MISC I-PER
OIL O I-LOC
Sept O I-ORG
DATA O I-LOC
Blue-chip O I-MISC
Salomon I-ORG I-PER
Bros I-ORG I-PER
. I-ORG O
Pirelli I-ORG O
Pirelli I-ORG O
Pirelli I-ORG I-PER
Pirelli I-ORG I-PER
Pirelli I-ORG I-LOC
Indosuez I-ORG I-LOC
Pirelli I-ORG O
Pirelli I-ORG I-LOC
GMT I-MISC O
Pirelli I-ORG O
Unicom I-ORG O
Pirelli I-ORG I-PER
FTO I-ORG O
FTO I-ORG O
OSCE I-ORG O
Cotti O I-PER
Chechnya I-LOC I-ORG
El I-ORG I-LOC
Al I-ORG I-LOC
THE I-LOC O
El I-ORG I-MISC
Al I-ORG I-MISC
El I-ORG I-LOC
Al I-ORG I-LOC
El I-ORG I-LOC
Al I-ORG I-LOC
Armenians I-MISC I-PER
Azeris I-MISC O
Azeris I-MISC I-ORG
Armenian O I-MISC
Group I-ORG O
Arctic I-MISC O
LONGYEAR I-LOC O
Longyear I-LOC I-PER
Onarheim I-LOC I-PER
Longyear I-LOC I-PER
Longyear I-LOC O
Ericsson I-ORG I-LOC
Ericsson I-ORG I-PER
AXE I-MISC I-ORG
Intelligent I-MISC I-PER
Network I-MISC I-PER
IN I-MISC O
Per I-PER O
South I-LOC I-ORG
China I-LOC I-ORG
KOMPAS I-ORG O
Wahono I-PER I-ORG
southern O I-ORG
Philippines I-LOC I-ORG
Philippine I-LOC I-MISC
Timor O I-LOC
Kia I-ORG I-PER
Tanjung I-LOC I-ORG
Priok I-LOC I-ORG
Kia I-ORG I-PER
REPUBLIKA I-ORG O
Jeans I-ORG O
Mate I-ORG I-PER
Corp I-ORG O
Jeans I-ORG O
Mate I-ORG I-PER
Corp I-ORG I-PER
Yamada I-ORG O
Apic I-ORG I-PER
Yamada I-ORG I-PER
Corp I-ORG I-PER
Huize I-LOC O
Changi I-LOC I-ORG
Prison I-LOC I-ORG
Jeerasak I-PER I-ORG
Densakul I-PER I-ORG
Nablus I-LOC O
President O I-ORG
Tono I-PER I-ORG
Eitel I-PER I-ORG
Holy I-LOC I-ORG
City I-LOC I-ORG
of I-LOC O
U.N. I-ORG O
Burj I-LOC I-MISC
al-Laqlaq I-LOC O
Society I-LOC O
REAL I-ORG O
SCRAPE O I-PER
SCRAPPY O I-MISC
LA I-LOC I-ORG
CORUNA I-LOC I-ORG
Real I-ORG O
Brazilian-born I-MISC I-PER
Spanish B-MISC I-PER
WIGAN I-ORG I-MISC
Israel I-LOC I-ORG
IRISH I-MISC O
Eschen I-LOC I-MISC
ESCHEN I-LOC I-ORG
Allenby I-PER I-LOC
FAROES I-LOC O
Jan I-PER O
Aki I-PER I-ORG
BIRMINGHAM I-ORG I-LOC
Trentino I-PER I-ORG
Kouznetsov I-PER I-ORG
Trentino I-PER I-ORG
World O I-MISC
Marion I-PER I-ORG
Clignet I-PER I-ORG
Record O I-MISC
Samokhvalova I-PER O
ENGLAND I-LOC O
GONZALEZ I-PER I-ORG
HOMERS O I-ORG
TWICE O I-ORG
AS O I-ORG
Chad I-PER I-LOC
Ogea I-PER O
Texas I-LOC I-ORG
Rivers I-PER O
Sierra I-PER I-ORG
Texas I-LOC I-ORG
Texas I-ORG I-LOC
Seattle I-ORG I-LOC
West I-LOC I-MISC
New I-LOC I-ORG
York I-LOC I-ORG
Pettite I-PER O
Ex-Yankee O I-ORG
Randy I-PER I-ORG
Velarde I-PER I-ORG
Incaviglia I-PER O
Seattle I-ORG I-LOC
Telgheder I-PER O
Kansas I-LOC I-ORG
City I-LOC I-ORG
Minnesota I-ORG I-LOC
ESSEX I-ORG I-LOC
KENT I-ORG I-PER
ENGLISH I-MISC I-LOC
WELSH I-MISC O
English I-MISC I-ORG
National I-MISC I-ORG
League I-MISC I-ORG
Harlequins I-ORG O
Sale I-ORG O
Wasps I-ORG I-PER
Bridgend I-ORG O
Treorchy I-ORG O
Newbridge I-ORG O
Hawick I-ORG O
Heriot I-ORG O
's I-ORG O
Jed-Forest I-ORG O
Melrose I-ORG I-PER
Stirling I-ORG I-PER
County O I-ORG
CARDIFF I-LOC I-ORG
BELFAST I-LOC O
LYNAGH I-PER I-ORG
SEALS O I-ORG
DWYER I-ORG I-LOC
LEICESTER I-ORG I-LOC
Wallaby I-ORG I-LOC
Lynagh I-PER O
Saracens I-ORG I-MISC
Gloucester I-ORG I-LOC
Bath I-ORG O
Orrell I-ORG I-PER
Wasps I-ORG O
Bristol I-ORG I-LOC
Inverness I-ORG I-LOC
Thistle I-ORG I-LOC
Inverness I-ORG I-LOC
Thistle I-ORG I-LOC
Brentford3 I-ORG O
Leeds I-LOC I-ORG
VANCOUVER I-LOC O
INDYCAR I-MISC O
IndyCar I-MISC O
Reynard I-ORG I-PER
Honda I-ORG I-PER
Lola I-ORG I-PER
Reynard I-ORG I-PER
Mercedes-Benz I-ORG I-PER
Reynard I-ORG I-PER
Mercedes-Benz I-ORG I-PER
Reynard I-ORG I-PER
Honda I-ORG I-PER
Penske I-ORG I-PER
Mercedes-Benz I-ORG I-PER
Jr O I-PER
Penske I-ORG I-PER
Mercedes-Benz I-ORG I-PER
Lola I-ORG I-PER
Honda I-ORG I-PER
Reynard I-ORG I-PER
Reynard I-ORG I-PER
Honda I-ORG I-PER
EDMONTON I-LOC O
CONCACAF I-ORG I-MISC
SPRINGBOKS I-ORG O
ALL I-ORG O
BLACK I-ORG O
SPELL O I-LOC
Ellis I-LOC I-ORG
Park I-LOC I-ORG
All I-ORG I-MISC
Black I-ORG I-MISC
Fullback O I-ORG
Andre I-PER I-ORG
Joubert I-PER I-ORG
Joubert I-PER O
der I-PER O
Honiball I-PER O
All I-ORG I-MISC
Black I-ORG I-MISC
der I-PER O
All I-ORG I-MISC
Black I-ORG I-MISC
Venter I-PER I-ORG
ALL I-ORG O
BLACKS I-ORG O
DISSOLVES O I-MISC
NATIONAL O I-MISC
TEAM O I-MISC
AFTER O I-MISC
NOUAKCHOTT I-LOC O
North I-MISC I-ORG
Africans I-MISC I-ORG
BENIN I-LOC O
NOUAKCHOTT I-LOC O
( I-ORG O
) I-ORG O
( I-ORG O
L I-ORG I-LOC
) I-ORG O
1 O I-ORG
) I-ORG O
Rad I-ORG I-PER
( I-ORG O
B I-ORG O
) I-ORG O
Proleter I-ORG I-PER
( I-ORG O
) I-ORG O
( I-ORG O
B I-ORG O
) I-ORG O
) I-ORG O
Spartak I-ORG I-PER
( I-ORG O
B I-ORG O
) I-ORG O
INCE I-PER I-ORG
EXPOSED O I-ORG
BY O I-ORG
GASCOIGNE I-PER I-ORG
Chisinau I-LOC I-ORG
TROFEJ I-MISC O
BEOGRAD I-MISC O
TOURNAMENT I-MISC O
Trofej I-MISC I-ORG
Beograd I-MISC I-ORG
96 I-MISC O
TROFEJ I-MISC O
BEOGRAD I-MISC O
TOURNAMENT I-MISC O
Trofej I-MISC I-ORG
Beograd I-MISC I-ORG
96 I-MISC O
YEREVAN I-LOC I-ORG
BAKU I-LOC O
Trofej I-MISC I-ORG
Beograd I-MISC I-ORG
96 I-MISC O
RIGA I-LOC I-ORG
MINSK I-LOC I-ORG
CHISINAU I-LOC O
Under-21 O I-MISC
HILL I-PER O
JANSHER I-PER I-MISC
Controversial O I-LOC
Australian I-MISC O
Hong I-MISC I-LOC
Kong I-MISC I-LOC
Open I-MISC I-LOC
Hong I-MISC I-LOC
Kong I-MISC I-LOC
Open I-MISC I-LOC
Hong I-MISC I-LOC
Kong I-MISC I-LOC
Open I-MISC I-LOC
PARNEVIK I-PER O
GREATER I-MISC I-LOC
MILWAUKEE I-MISC I-LOC
OPEN I-MISC I-LOC
MILWAUKEE I-LOC I-ORG
Greater I-MISC O
Parnevik I-PER O
Brown I-LOC I-ORG
Deer I-LOC I-ORG
Park I-LOC I-ORG
Golf I-LOC I-ORG
Course I-LOC I-ORG
victory O I-MISC
1993 I-MISC O
Tiger I-PER I-ORG
Woods I-PER I-ORG
Parnevik I-PER O
1997 I-MISC O
Fed I-MISC I-ORG
Cup I-MISC I-ORG
Life O I-ORG
Nagoya I-LOC O
Fed I-MISC I-ORG
Cup I-MISC I-ORG
King I-PER O
King I-PER O
Fed I-MISC I-ORG
Cup I-MISC I-ORG
King I-PER O
King I-PER O
King I-PER O
King I-PER O
1997 I-MISC O
1997 I-MISC O
Fed I-MISC I-ORG
Cup I-MISC I-ORG
World O I-ORG
Group O I-ORG
World O I-ORG
Group O I-ORG
II O I-ORG
EL I-LOC I-ORG
SALVADOR I-LOC I-ORG
LOS I-LOC I-ORG
ANGELES I-LOC I-ORG
El I-LOC I-ORG
Salvador I-LOC I-ORG
El I-LOC I-ORG
Salvador I-LOC I-ORG
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
YORK I-ORG I-LOC
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
YORK I-ORG I-LOC
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
YORK I-ORG I-LOC
BROWN I-PER I-ORG
LOWERS O I-ORG
ERA I-MISC I-ORG
CINCINNATI I-LOC I-ORG
Major O I-MISC
Florida I-ORG I-LOC
( I-PER O
) I-PER O
( I-PER O
Jerry I-PER I-MISC
) I-PER O
Koosman I-PER O
Los I-ORG I-LOC
Angeles I-ORG I-LOC
Atlanta I-ORG I-LOC
Montreal I-LOC I-ORG
Montreal I-LOC I-ORG
Colorado I-ORG I-LOC
Wall I-PER I-LOC
QUIETLY O I-LOC
Karbacher I-PER O
NASEEM I-PER O
WBO I-ORG O
Marasek I-PER O
Scotland I-LOC I-MISC
VERDICT O I-LOC
IBF I-ORG O
Mexican I-MISC I-ORG
Djorkaeff I-PER O
Ouedec I-PER O
Espanyol I-ORG O
Barcelona I-LOC I-ORG
del I-PER O
Ouedec I-PER O
Djorkaeff I-PER I-LOC
German I-PER I-MISC
del I-PER O
CROWD O I-LOC
1998 I-MISC O
Degryse I-PER O
Recber I-PER O
division I-MISC O
Attendancce O I-ORG
division I-MISC O
SCOTLAND I-LOC O
KNOCK-OUT O I-PER
MILLER I-PER O
WBA I-ORG O
Miller I-PER I-LOC
Miller I-PER I-ORG
Netherlands I-LOC O
MILLER I-PER O
WBA I-ORG O
WBA I-ORG O
TATTERSALLS I-MISC O
BREEDERS I-MISC O
Tattersalls I-MISC I-ORG
Breeders I-MISC I-ORG
Stakes I-MISC O
The I-LOC O
Stamper I-PER I-ORG
KLINSMANN I-PER O
1998 I-MISC O
U-21 O I-MISC
Lithuania I-LOC I-ORG
Under-21 O I-MISC
IRA I-ORG O
The I-ORG O
Libran I-MISC O
Thatcher I-PER O
Iron I-PER I-LOC
Lady I-PER I-LOC
My I-MISC O
Turn I-MISC O
Queen O I-PER
I I-PER O
Duke O I-PER
Austrians I-MISC O
Eugene I-ORG I-PER
Treaty I-MISC I-ORG
of I-MISC O
Baden I-MISC I-LOC
Holy O I-MISC
Emperor O I-MISC
War I-MISC O
of I-MISC O
Succession I-MISC O
Alsace I-LOC I-PER
Strasbourg I-LOC I-ORG
Breisach I-LOC O
Kehl I-LOC I-PER
Borodino I-LOC I-ORG
I I-PER O
Liberal I-MISC I-ORG
Transvaal I-LOC I-ORG
of I-ORG O
Trades I-MISC I-ORG
Disputes I-MISC I-ORG
Act I-MISC I-ORG
Red I-MISC I-ORG
Shirts I-MISC I-ORG
Austrians I-MISC I-ORG
Boxer I-MISC O
Rising I-MISC O
Peking I-MISC I-ORG
Protocol I-MISC I-ORG
Boxer I-MISC O
Viva I-MISC I-PER
Zapata I-MISC I-PER
On I-MISC O
the I-MISC O
Waterfront I-MISC O
Ice I-MISC O
Cold I-MISC I-PER
in I-MISC O
Alex I-MISC I-LOC
Lawrence I-MISC I-PER
of I-MISC O
Arabia I-MISC I-LOC
Cardinal O I-PER
Anne I-MISC I-PER
of I-MISC O
a I-MISC O
Thousand I-MISC I-ORG
Days I-MISC I-ORG
I I-PER O
Blitz I-MISC I-PER
London I-LOC O
Anglicans I-MISC O
Saudi I-MISC I-LOC
Kuwaiti I-MISC I-LOC
( I-PER O
A.J.P. I-PER I-LOC
) I-PER O
Taylor I-PER I-ORG
Stars I-MISC I-ORG
and I-MISC O
Stripes I-MISC I-ORG
England I-LOC O
Holland I-PER O
Holland I-PER O
narrowly O I-ORG
STIRLING I-LOC O
Scots I-MISC O
Scottish I-ORG I-MISC
National I-ORG I-MISC
Party I-ORG I-MISC
Arbil I-LOC O
Flight I-MISC O
London-based I-MISC O
Iraqi I-ORG I-MISC
National I-ORG I-MISC
Congress I-ORG I-MISC
Washington I-LOC I-PER
) O I-ORG
SEOUL I-LOC O
Lotte I-ORG I-PER
Afrikaners B-MISC I-MISC
Afrikaners O I-ORG
Northern I-LOC I-ORG
Cape I-LOC I-ORG
Afrikaners I-MISC I-ORG
Certain O I-MISC
Viljoen I-PER O
African I-ORG I-MISC
National I-ORG I-MISC
Congress I-ORG I-MISC
Northern I-LOC I-ORG
Cape I-LOC I-ORG
Coloureds O I-PER
Afrikaans I-MISC O
Mahala I-LOC I-PER
NATO I-ORG I-MISC
URUS-MARTAN I-LOC I-PER
Urus-Martan I-LOC O
mainly-Moslem I-MISC O
Urus-Martan I-LOC O
Urus-Martan I-LOC I-PER
Mouldi I-PER I-ORG
Mamatuyev I-PER I-ORG
Nurbika I-PER O
God I-PER O
Akhbar I-PER O
Freedom O I-ORG
Sheriat I-MISC O
Islamic I-MISC I-LOC
Hachette I-ORG I-PER
Multico I-ORG I-PER
BRE I-ORG I-LOC
division I-MISC O
Hachette I-ORG I-PER
UWP I-ORG O
Ruch I-ORG O
UWP-Hachette I-ORG O
SPC I-ORG I-MISC
SPC I-ORG I-LOC
UWP-Hachette I-ORG O
MOSCOW I-LOC O
Sergiyev I-LOC O
Posad I-LOC I-PER
HAVANA I-LOC I-ORG
Bertillon I-MISC O
166 I-MISC O
pre-Castro I-MISC O
In I-MISC O
the I-MISC O
Year I-MISC O
of I-MISC O
January I-MISC O
The I-MISC O
Sleeping I-MISC O
Bread I-MISC O
The I-MISC O
Decaying I-MISC I-ORG
Mansion I-MISC I-ORG
A I-MISC O
World I-MISC O
of I-MISC O
Things I-MISC O
The I-MISC O
Knot I-MISC I-LOC
Soul I-MISC O
Alone I-MISC O
A I-MISC O
Woman I-MISC O
Granma I-ORG I-PER
Sleeping I-MISC O
Bread I-MISC O
Prensa I-ORG O
Latina I-ORG I-PER
SANTIAGO I-PER I-ORG
Michoacan I-LOC I-MISC
Morelia I-LOC I-PER
AK-47s I-MISC I-PER
in I-ORG O
China I-ORG I-LOC
Strike I-MISC O
Hard I-MISC O
Philippine I-LOC I-MISC
Suharto I-PER I-ORG
Philippine I-LOC I-MISC
RANGOON I-LOC I-ORG
San I-PER I-ORG
Suu I-PER I-ORG
Kyi I-PER I-ORG
National I-ORG I-MISC
League I-ORG I-MISC
for I-ORG O
Democracy I-ORG O
NLD I-ORG I-LOC
State I-ORG I-MISC
Law I-ORG I-MISC
and I-ORG O
Order I-ORG O
Insein I-LOC O
Prison I-LOC I-PER
Than I-PER O
( I-PER O
Leo I-PER I-LOC
) I-PER O
Nichols I-PER I-ORG
Chemical I-ORG O
BEIJING I-LOC O
Dow I-ORG I-MISC
Chemical I-ORG I-MISC
Co I-ORG I-MISC
Tianjin I-LOC O
Multinational O I-MISC
Mobil I-ORG I-LOC
N. I-LOC I-PER
Korea I-LOC I-ORG
SEOUL I-LOC O
North I-ORG I-MISC
Korean I-ORG I-MISC
Red I-ORG I-MISC
Cross I-ORG I-MISC
War O I-MISC
Yonhap I-ORG I-MISC
War O I-MISC
BEIJING I-LOC O
in I-ORG O
China I-ORG I-LOC
1966-76 I-MISC O
Hangzhou I-LOC I-MISC
BEIJING I-LOC O
in I-ORG O
China I-ORG I-LOC
High I-ORG O
Court I-ORG O
Hong I-ORG I-LOC
Kong I-ORG I-LOC
Standard I-ORG I-LOC
Chinese I-MISC I-ORG
BEIJING I-LOC O
Wuhan I-LOC O
Guangzhou I-LOC O
ISTANBUL I-LOC I-ORG
Northern O I-ORG
Iraq I-LOC I-ORG
in I-ORG O
Lebanon I-ORG I-LOC
UNIFIL I-ORG I-LOC
Sikhin I-LOC I-MISC
of I-ORG O
aid-U.N. I-MISC O
BAGHDAD I-LOC I-ORG
Arbil I-LOC O
Turkish-operated O I-MISC
Bahraini I-LOC I-MISC
al-Daih I-LOC O
BAGHDAD I-LOC I-ORG
Barzani I-PER I-LOC
Arbil I-LOC O
KDP-controlled O I-MISC
Arbil I-LOC O
BAGHDAD I-LOC I-ORG
al-Abidine I-PER O
DETROIT I-LOC I-ORG
Interstate I-LOC I-MISC
95 I-LOC O
East I-LOC I-ORG
Coast I-LOC I-ORG
Interstates I-LOC I-ORG
80 I-LOC O
90 I-LOC O
Interstate I-LOC I-ORG
5 I-LOC O
Bag O I-MISC
Buckled O I-PER
Kids O I-PER
ROCHESTER I-LOC O
Rochester I-LOC I-PER
Motel O I-LOC
Boston I-LOC I-ORG
Carl I-MISC I-PER
Vinson I-MISC I-PER
Enterprise I-MISC I-ORG
Mediterranean I-MISC I-LOC
Troy I-LOC I-PER
U.S. I-LOC I-MISC
F I-MISC O
/ I-MISC O
A-18 I-MISC O
Vinson I-MISC I-PER
Enterprise I-MISC I-LOC
F-15 I-MISC O
Marines I-MISC I-ORG
U.S. I-LOC I-MISC
U.S. I-LOC I-MISC
Marines I-MISC I-ORG
Group I-ORG O
Carl I-MISC I-PER
Vinson I-MISC I-PER
U.S. I-LOC I-MISC
Bonn I-LOC I-PER
Spiegel I-ORG O
Nyerere I-PER O
' I-ORG O
Nyerere I-PER I-LOC
Great I-LOC I-MISC
Lakes I-LOC I-MISC
Artisans I-MISC I-ORG
for I-MISC O
Peace I-MISC I-LOC
' I-ORG O
's O I-ORG
Chatelet I-LOC I-PER
Chatelineaux I-LOC I-ORG
Controversial O I-ORG
VENICE O I-LOC
Michael I-MISC I-PER
Collins I-MISC I-PER
Venice I-MISC I-ORG
Film I-MISC I-ORG
Festival I-MISC I-ORG
Northern I-LOC I-ORG
Ireland I-LOC I-ORG
Jordan I-PER I-LOC
Jordan I-PER I-LOC
Warner I-ORG I-PER
Bros I-ORG I-PER
Jordan I-PER I-LOC
The I-MISC O
Crying I-MISC I-ORG
Game I-MISC I-ORG
IRA I-ORG I-LOC
Yitzak I-PER O
Jordan I-PER I-LOC
Northern I-MISC I-ORG
Ireland-born I-MISC I-ORG
Oscar I-PER O
Schindler I-MISC I-PER
's I-MISC O
List I-MISC O
Jordan I-PER I-LOC
Roberts I-PER I-LOC
Jordan I-PER I-LOC
Jordan I-PER I-LOC
Collins I-PER I-LOC
Michael I-MISC I-PER
Collins I-MISC I-PER
Jordan I-PER I-LOC
Broker O I-ORG
Khurshid I-PER I-ORG
Alam I-PER I-ORG
IDLC I-ORG I-LOC
Bangladesh I-ORG I-LOC
Lamps I-ORG I-LOC
