JAPAN I-LOC O
LUCKY O I-ORG
CHINA I-PER I-ORG
AL-AIN I-LOC I-PER
Uzbekistan I-LOC I-ORG
Hiroshige I-PER O
Defender O I-PER
Hosts O I-MISC
ITALY I-LOC O
1995 I-MISC O
JAPAN I-LOC I-ORG
AL-AIN I-LOC I-PER
Defender O I-PER
Takagi I-PER O
Honda I-PER I-ORG
al-Boushi I-PER O
FREESTYLE O I-ORG
SKIING-WORLD I-MISC I-ORG
CUP I-MISC I-ORG
MOGUL O I-ORG
GROUP O I-MISC
AL-AIN I-LOC I-PER
Japan I-LOC I-ORG
Syria I-LOC I-ORG
Uzbekistan I-LOC I-ORG
Uzbekistan I-LOC I-ORG
Inzamamul I-PER O
Doull I-PER O
BLINKER I-PER O
BAN O I-PER
Wednesday I-ORG O
Blinker I-PER O
BOWYER I-PER I-ORG
McDonald I-ORG I-LOC
's I-ORG O
Yorkshire I-LOC I-ORG
EUROLEAGUE I-MISC O
EuroLeague I-MISC O
Maccabi I-ORG O
Limoges I-ORG I-PER
Panionios I-ORG O
Cibona I-ORG O
Zagreb I-ORG I-LOC
Charleroi I-ORG I-LOC
Panathinaikos I-ORG I-PER
Ljubljana I-ORG I-LOC
Villeurbanne I-ORG I-PER
Split I-ORG I-LOC
Pau-Orthez I-ORG I-PER
Kinder I-ORG I-PER
Bologna I-ORG I-PER
Sevilla I-ORG I-PER
LITTLE I-PER I-LOC
Barbarians I-ORG O
Little I-PER I-LOC
Wallabies I-ORG O
Barbarians I-ORG I-LOC
Twickenham I-LOC O
League O I-MISC
All I-ORG I-MISC
Black I-ORG I-MISC
Barbarians I-ORG O
Burke I-PER I-LOC
ZIMBABWE I-MISC I-LOC
OPEN I-MISC O
Chapman I-LOC I-PER
Golf I-LOC I-PER
Club I-LOC O
South I-MISC I-LOC
African I-MISC I-LOC
Botes I-PER O
da I-PER O
UNCAPPED O I-ORG
Iordanescu I-PER O
League O I-MISC
REUTER I-ORG I-PER
ENDURES O I-ORG
Chanderpaul I-PER O
INDIES I-LOC O
Moody I-PER I-ORG
Moody I-PER I-ORG
Moody I-PER I-ORG
Moody I-PER I-ORG
INDIES I-LOC O
Melbourne I-LOC I-ORG
Cricket I-LOC I-ORG
Ground I-LOC I-ORG
INDIES I-LOC O
SHEFFIELD I-MISC I-LOC
SHIELD I-MISC O
SCORE O I-LOC
Sheffield I-MISC I-ORG
Shield I-MISC I-ORG
Victoria I-ORG I-PER
SUFFERS O I-ORG
Moody I-PER I-ORG
Melbourne I-LOC I-ORG
Cricket I-LOC I-ORG
Ground I-LOC I-ORG
Tour O I-MISC
Lloyd I-PER I-ORG
on O I-ORG
Lloyd I-PER I-ORG
Sydney I-LOC I-ORG
Cricket I-LOC I-ORG
Ground I-LOC I-ORG
INDIES I-LOC O
Melbourne I-LOC I-ORG
Cricket O I-ORG
Ground O I-ORG
Junior I-PER O
BALI I-LOC I-ORG
Sun I-PER I-ORG
Jun I-PER O
Budi I-PER I-ORG
Santoso I-PER I-ORG
ARAB I-MISC I-LOC
stadium I-LOC O
Arab I-ORG I-MISC
Contractors I-ORG O
Sodigraf I-ORG O
League I-ORG I-MISC
EASTERN O I-MISC
CONFERENCE O I-MISC
T O I-ORG
GF O I-ORG
GA O I-ORG
PTS O I-ORG
OTTAWA I-ORG I-LOC
DIVISION O I-LOC
T O I-ORG
GF O I-ORG
GA O I-ORG
PTS O I-ORG
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
JERSEY I-ORG I-LOC
WASHINGTON I-ORG I-LOC
NY I-ORG O
RANGERS I-ORG O
NY I-ORG O
ISLANDERS I-ORG O
WESTERN O I-MISC
CONFERENCE O I-MISC
T O I-ORG
GF O I-ORG
GA O I-ORG
PTS O I-ORG
DALLAS I-ORG I-LOC
DIVISION O I-LOC
T O I-ORG
GF O I-ORG
GA O I-ORG
PTS O I-ORG
VANCOUVER I-ORG I-LOC
EDMONTON I-ORG O
SAN I-ORG I-LOC
JOSE I-ORG I-LOC
CALGARY I-ORG I-LOC
NY I-ORG I-LOC
RANGERS I-ORG O
OTTAWA I-ORG I-LOC
NHL I-ORG I-LOC
League I-ORG I-LOC
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
JERSEY I-ORG I-LOC
Tampa I-ORG I-LOC
Bay I-ORG O
AMERICAN O I-ORG
FOOTBALL-COLTS O I-ORG
CLOBBER O I-ORG
INDIANAPOLIS I-LOC I-ORG
Indianapolis I-ORG I-LOC
Colts I-ORG O
Eagles I-ORG I-MISC
Cincinnati I-LOC I-ORG
Philadelphia I-LOC I-ORG
NFC O I-MISC
East O I-MISC
Dallas I-ORG I-LOC
Cowboys I-ORG I-LOC
Washington I-ORG I-LOC
Redskins I-ORG I-LOC
Arizona I-ORG I-LOC
Green I-ORG I-PER
Bay I-ORG I-PER
Packers I-ORG I-PER
Philadelphia I-LOC I-ORG
National I-ORG I-LOC
EASTERN O I-MISC
CONFERENCE O I-MISC
DIVISION O I-LOC
MIAMI I-ORG I-LOC
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
YORK I-ORG I-LOC
WASHINGTON I-ORG I-LOC
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
JERSEY I-ORG I-LOC
CENTRAL O I-MISC
DIVISION O I-MISC
CHICAGO I-ORG I-LOC
CHARLOTTE I-ORG O
WESTERN O I-MISC
CONFERENCE O I-MISC
DENVER I-ORG I-PER
SAN I-ORG I-LOC
ANTONIO I-ORG I-LOC
DIVISION O I-LOC
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
JERSEY I-ORG I-LOC
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
YORK I-ORG I-LOC
VANCOUVER I-ORG I-LOC
LA I-LOC I-ORG
LAKERS I-LOC O
AMERICAN O I-ORG
FOOTBALL-STANDINGS O I-ORG
FOOTBALL O I-MISC
CONFERENCE O I-MISC
EASTERN O I-MISC
DIVISION O I-MISC
T O I-ORG
PF O I-ORG
PA O I-ORG
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
ENGLAND I-ORG I-LOC
NY I-ORG O
JETS I-ORG O
CENTRAL O I-MISC
DIVISION O I-MISC
T O I-ORG
PF O I-ORG
JACKSONVILLE I-ORG I-LOC
WESTERN O I-MISC
DIVISION O I-MISC
T O I-ORG
PF O I-ORG
PA O I-ORG
X-DENVER I-MISC I-ORG
NATIONAL O I-MISC
FOOTBALL O I-MISC
CONFERENCE O I-MISC
EASTERN O I-MISC
DIVISION O I-MISC
T O I-ORG
PF O I-ORG
PA O I-ORG
NY I-ORG O
CENTRAL O I-MISC
DIVISION O I-MISC
T O I-ORG
PF O I-ORG
PA O I-ORG
Y-GREEN I-MISC I-ORG
BAY I-MISC I-ORG
WESTERN O I-MISC
DIVISION O I-MISC
T O I-ORG
PF O I-ORG
PA O I-ORG
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
ORLEANS I-ORG O
CLINCHED O I-ORG
PLAYOFF O I-ORG
BERTH O I-ORG
DENVER I-ORG I-PER
JACKSONVILLE I-ORG I-LOC
WASHINGTON I-ORG I-LOC
DALLAS I-ORG I-LOC
AMERICAN O I-ORG
FOOTBALL-THURSDAY O I-ORG
Football I-LOC I-ORG
League I-LOC I-MISC
AMERICAN O I-ORG
FOOTBALL-OHIO I-MISC I-ORG
STATE I-MISC I-ORG
'S O I-ORG
PACE I-PER I-ORG
FIRST O I-ORG
REPEAT O I-ORG
LOMBARDI I-MISC I-ORG
AWARD I-MISC I-ORG
WINNER O I-ORG
HOUSTON I-LOC I-ORG
Lombardi I-MISC I-PER
Award I-MISC I-PER
Pace I-PER O
State I-ORG O
Pace I-PER O
Pace I-PER O
Virginia I-ORG I-LOC
Tech I-ORG O
State I-ORG O
Nebraska I-ORG I-LOC
Lombardi I-MISC I-PER
Award I-MISC I-PER
Green I-ORG I-PER
16 O I-ORG
1. I-ORG O
FC I-ORG O
Hamburger I-ORG I-PER
Starbuck O I-PER
Konterman I-PER I-ORG
der I-PER O
Karlsruhe I-LOC I-ORG
Dundee I-ORG I-PER
Freiburg I-LOC I-ORG
WEAH I-PER O
HEAD-BUTT O I-PER
PORTUGAL I-LOC O
COSTA I-PER I-LOC
Costa I-PER I-LOC
Barcelona I-ORG I-LOC
Oviedo I-ORG I-PER
Salamanca I-ORG I-LOC
REAL I-ORG O
MADRID I-ORG I-LOC
Real B-ORG I-ORG
Barcelona B-ORG I-ORG
Real B-ORG I-ORG
Barcelona B-ORG I-ORG
Barcelona B-ORG I-ORG
JosepGuardiola I-PER O
laPena I-PER O
AbelardoFernandez I-PER O
SHOWCASE-FANS O I-PER
FACE O I-ORG
BREATHALYSER O I-ORG
stadium I-LOC O
Real I-MISC I-ORG
Madrid-Barcelona I-MISC I-ORG
Rayo I-ORG I-PER
Valencia I-ORG I-LOC
Espanyol I-ORG O
Gijon O I-ORG
Logrones I-ORG O
Compostela I-ORG O
HAVELANGE I-PER I-ORG
STANDS O I-ORG
WEAH I-PER O
George I-PER I-ORG
Weah I-PER I-ORG
Gazzetta I-ORG O
dello I-ORG O
Costa I-PER I-LOC
Costa I-PER I-LOC
UEFA I-ORG I-MISC
Costa I-PER I-LOC
Costa I-PER I-LOC
Costa I-PER I-LOC
Weah I-PER O
GUNMEN O I-ORG
WOUND O I-ORG
MANCHESTER I-ORG I-LOC
UNITED I-ORG I-LOC
FANS O I-LOC
Serie B-MISC I-MISC
A I-MISC O
Bologna I-ORG I-PER
Igor I-PER I-MISC
Kolyvanov I-PER I-MISC
Bologna I-ORG I-PER
Napoli I-ORG I-PER
Bottom O I-LOC
Reggiana I-ORG O
German I-MISC I-PER
Milan I-PER I-ORG
Rapajic I-PER I-ORG
Lazio I-ORG I-PER
AS I-ORG O
' I-MISC O
Napoli I-ORG I-PER
Verona I-ORG I-PER
Verona I-ORG I-PER
Verona I-ORG I-PER
Atlalanta I-ORG I-PER
Vicenza I-ORG O
Inter I-ORG I-LOC
EUROLEAGUE I-MISC O
EuroLeague I-MISC O
Charleroi I-ORG I-LOC
Charleroi I-ORG I-LOC
Estudiantes I-ORG O
Kinder I-ORG I-PER
Bologna I-ORG I-PER
EYLES I-PER I-ORG
WITHIN O I-ORG
Mahindra I-MISC I-ORG
International I-MISC I-ORG
INTERNATIONAL I-MISC O
Mahindra I-MISC I-ORG
International I-MISC I-ORG
S.AFRICA I-MISC O
ZULU I-MISC O
DURBAN I-PER I-LOC
Zulu I-MISC O
African I-ORG I-MISC
National I-ORG I-MISC
Congress I-ORG I-MISC
KwaZulu-Natal I-LOC O
Zulu I-MISC I-ORG
Mangosuthu I-PER I-ORG
Buthelezi I-PER I-ORG
HAVEL I-PER I-ORG
PRAISES O I-ORG
CZECH I-MISC I-ORG
ALBRIGHT I-PER O
Communists I-MISC I-ORG
Czech I-LOC I-MISC
Albright I-PER I-LOC
trans-Atlantic I-MISC O
Albright I-PER I-LOC
Albright I-PER I-LOC
Czechs I-MISC I-ORG
AFTERNOON O I-ORG
HEALINES O I-ORG
AT O I-ORG
Social I-ORG I-MISC
Democratic I-ORG I-MISC
Union I-ORG I-MISC
Hungarian I-ORG I-MISC
Democratic I-ORG I-MISC
Union I-ORG I-MISC
UDMR I-ORG I-LOC
UDMR I-ORG I-LOC
Timisoara I-LOC O
CZECH I-MISC I-LOC
VICE-PM O I-LOC
DEBATE O I-ORG
AT O I-ORG
Czech I-ORG I-LOC
Civic I-ORG I-LOC
Democratic I-ORG I-LOC
Party I-ORG I-LOC
ODS I-ORG I-LOC
Czech I-LOC I-MISC
Brno I-LOC O
Zieleniec I-PER O
post-Communist I-MISC O
Czech I-LOC I-MISC
Jews B-MISC I-MISC
Holocaust I-MISC I-LOC
German B-MISC I-MISC
Holocaust I-MISC O
FDP I-ORG I-LOC
INTERVIEW-ZYWIEC I-MISC I-ORG
BIG O I-ORG
Zywiec I-ORG O
Zywiec I-ORG O
Zaklady I-ORG O
Piwowarskie I-ORG I-PER
w I-ORG O
Zywcu I-ORG I-PER
van O I-PER
Zywiec I-ORG I-PER
Heineken I-ORG I-PER
Carlsberg I-ORG I-PER
Okocim I-ORG I-LOC
South I-ORG I-MISC
African I-ORG I-MISC
Breweries I-ORG I-MISC
Ltd I-ORG I-MISC
SAB I-ORG O
Brewpole I-ORG O
BV I-ORG I-LOC
Elbrewery I-ORG I-PER
Company I-ORG I-PER
Ltd. I-ORG I-PER
EB I-ORG I-LOC
Zywiec I-ORG O
Czech I-LOC I-MISC
CEFTA I-ORG O
Czech I-LOC I-MISC
Czech I-LOC I-MISC
Zywiec I-ORG I-PER
Okocim I-ORG O
Carlsberg I-ORG O
Zywiec I-ORG I-PER
Heineken I-ORG I-PER
Zywiec I-ORG I-PER
Full I-MISC I-PER
Light I-MISC I-PER
van O I-PER
Heineken I-ORG I-PER
Zywiec I-ORG I-PER
WORSENS O I-ORG
Department I-ORG O
of I-ORG O
DOT I-ORG O
Tambang I-ORG O
Timah I-ORG O
Receipt O I-PER
Telkom I-ORG O
Telkom I-ORG I-LOC
BELFAST I-LOC O
Irish I-ORG I-MISC
Republican I-ORG I-MISC
Army I-ORG I-MISC
Belfast I-LOC O
trans-Atlantic I-MISC O
Monopolies I-ORG O
and I-ORG O
Trade I-ORG O
and I-ORG O
Industry I-ORG O
trans-Atlantic I-MISC O
of I-ORG O
Fair I-ORG I-MISC
Trading I-ORG I-MISC
AA I-ORG O
trans-Atlantic I-MISC O
American I-ORG I-MISC
USAir I-ORG O
trans-Atlantic I-MISC O
American I-ORG I-MISC
London-to-Boston I-MISC O
of I-ORG O
American I-ORG O
of I-ORG O
Fair I-ORG I-MISC
Trading I-ORG I-MISC
Jan. O I-ORG
Sale I-ORG O
Grammar I-ORG O
School I-ORG O
Manchester I-LOC I-ORG
Lanarkshire I-LOC I-MISC
Major I-PER O
office-Conservatives I-MISC O
Conservative I-MISC O
Gorst I-PER O
Major I-PER O
Street I-LOC O
MP O I-LOC
Gorst I-PER O
Data I-ORG O
Private O I-ORG
Finance O I-ORG
Initiative O I-ORG
EDS I-ORG O
Oceanic I-LOC I-ORG
Control I-LOC I-ORG
Centre I-LOC I-ORG
National I-ORG I-MISC
Air I-ORG I-MISC
Traffic I-ORG I-MISC
Services I-ORG I-MISC
Ltd I-ORG I-MISC
NATS I-ORG I-LOC
Australia-West I-MISC I-LOC
Indies I-MISC I-LOC
Chanderpaul I-PER I-ORG
Cwt O I-LOC
MINIMUM O I-ORG
Manitoba I-ORG I-LOC
Price O I-ORG
Index O I-ORG
Manitoba I-ORG I-LOC
Hog O I-MISC
CAN I-LOC O
Canadian I-MISC I-ORG
West O I-ORG
Coast O I-ORG
Vessel O I-ORG
Loadings O I-ORG
CWB O I-ORG
West O I-MISC
Coast O I-MISC
West O I-ORG
Coast O I-ORG
East O I-ORG
Coast O I-ORG
Port O I-ORG
Loading O I-ORG
Waiting O I-ORG
Vancouver I-LOC I-ORG
New I-LOC I-ORG
York I-LOC I-ORG
New I-LOC I-ORG
York I-LOC I-ORG
Maritime I-MISC I-LOC
Queen I-MISC O
Dampier I-LOC O
Kaohsiung I-LOC O
Desk O I-ORG
Clean O I-MISC
GMT I-MISC O
WESTERN O I-LOC
HEMISPHERE O I-LOC
Danila I-MISC I-PER
Mobil I-ORG O
Desk O I-ORG
GMT I-MISC O
MIDEAST O I-LOC
Resource I-MISC O
Ras I-LOC I-PER
Tanura I-LOC O
Mobil I-ORG I-LOC
MEDITERRANEAN I-MISC O
Lula I-MISC O
I I-MISC O
Sidi I-LOC I-ORG
Kreir I-LOC O
Augusta I-LOC I-PER
W100 O I-PER
Exxon I-ORG I-PER
Spetses I-MISC O
Sidi I-LOC I-ORG
Kreir I-LOC O
Augusta I-LOC I-PER
W97.50 O I-PER
Exxon I-ORG I-PER
Mesipia I-MISC I-ORG
Bajaia I-LOC O
Fos I-LOC I-PER
W105 O I-PER
Exxon I-ORG I-PER
New I-LOC I-ORG
York I-LOC I-ORG
City I-LOC I-ORG
Goldman I-ORG I-PER
, I-ORG O
Sachs I-ORG I-PER
Euronotes I-MISC O
Wall I-LOC I-ORG
St I-LOC I-ORG
Santa I-LOC I-PER
Fe I-LOC I-PER
tops O I-ORG
Wall I-LOC I-ORG
Street I-LOC I-ORG
Santa I-ORG I-PER
Santa I-ORG I-LOC
Fe I-ORG I-LOC
Newmont I-ORG I-PER
Santa I-ORG I-PER
Fe I-ORG I-PER
Newmont I-ORG I-LOC
Newmont I-ORG I-LOC
Santa I-ORG I-LOC
Fe I-ORG I-LOC
Newmont I-ORG I-PER
Santa I-ORG I-PER
Fe I-ORG I-PER
Newmont I-ORG I-PER
Santa I-ORG I-LOC
Fe I-ORG I-LOC
Nevada I-LOC I-MISC
Newmont I-ORG O
Newmont I-ORG I-PER
Santa I-ORG I-LOC
Fe I-ORG I-LOC
Santa I-ORG I-PER
Fe I-ORG O
Busang I-ORG O
Santa I-ORG I-PER
Fe I-ORG I-PER
Nevada I-LOC I-PER
Homestake I-ORG O
Homestake I-ORG I-PER
Santa I-ORG I-PER
Fe I-ORG I-PER
N.M. I-LOC O
Santa I-ORG I-PER
Fe I-ORG I-PER
Newmont I-ORG O
Newmont I-ORG I-PER
Santa I-ORG I-PER
Fe I-ORG I-PER
Homestake I-ORG O
Newmont I-ORG O
Santa I-ORG I-LOC
Fe I-ORG I-LOC
Newmont-Santa I-MISC O
Fe I-MISC O
Newmont I-ORG I-PER
Newmont I-ORG I-MISC
Santa I-ORG I-LOC
Fe I-ORG I-LOC
New I-ORG I-LOC
York I-ORG I-LOC
Stock I-ORG I-LOC
Exchange I-ORG I-LOC
Newmonth I-ORG I-PER
Santa I-ORG I-PER
Fe I-ORG I-PER
Newmont I-ORG I-PER
Santa I-ORG I-PER
Fe I-ORG I-PER
Newmont I-ORG I-LOC
Newmont I-ORG I-PER
Santa I-ORG I-LOC
Fe I-ORG I-LOC
Wall I-ORG I-LOC
Street I-ORG I-LOC
Desk I-ORG I-LOC
Russ I-ORG I-PER
Berrie I-ORG I-PER
OAKLAND I-LOC I-ORG
Russ I-ORG I-PER
Berrie I-ORG I-PER
and I-ORG O
Lieutenant-General O I-ORG
Maurice I-PER I-ORG
Baril I-PER I-ORG
NGOs O I-ORG
Chapter O I-MISC
Seven O I-MISC
Chapter O I-MISC
Seven O I-MISC
Masisi O I-LOC
Bukavu I-LOC O
Kindu I-LOC I-PER
Kisangani I-LOC I-MISC
sans I-ORG O
PORT I-LOC O
LOUIS I-LOC O
Daniella I-MISC I-PER
Central I-LOC I-MISC
African I-LOC I-MISC
Republic I-LOC I-MISC
Central I-LOC I-ORG
African I-LOC I-ORG
Republic I-LOC I-ORG
Diouf I-PER O
Ex-minister O I-PER
BANGUI I-LOC I-ORG
Public O I-ORG
French-owned I-MISC O
Yakomas I-MISC O
Patasse I-PER I-LOC
Baya I-MISC O
Patasse I-PER O
Patasse I-PER O
Patasse I-PER O
Codos I-MISC O
Hospital O I-LOC
SAfrican I-MISC O
North I-LOC I-ORG
West I-LOC I-ORG
Meyers I-PER O
Pope O I-PER
Pope O I-PER
Pope O I-PER
Democratic I-ORG I-MISC
Church I-ORG O
Norilsk I-ORG I-LOC
Norilsk I-ORG O
Nickel I-ORG O
Norilsk I-ORG O
Rinaco I-ORG O
Plus I-ORG I-PER
Norilsk I-ORG O
United I-ORG I-LOC
City I-ORG I-LOC
Bank I-ORG I-LOC
Far O I-LOC
North O I-LOC
Norilsk I-ORG O
Norilsk I-ORG I-PER
Norilsk I-ORG O
Norilsk I-ORG I-PER
Norilsk I-ORG I-LOC
Norilsk I-ORG I-PER
Norilsk I-ORG O
Norilsk I-ORG O
Krasnoyarsk I-LOC O
Norilsk I-ORG O
Norilsk I-ORG I-PER
Uneximbank I-ORG I-PER
Interrosimpex I-ORG O
Norilsk I-ORG O
Uneximbank I-ORG O
Norilsk I-ORG I-PER
First O I-MISC
Deputy O I-MISC
Russian-U.S. I-MISC O
Soviet-led I-MISC I-ORG
Warsaw B-MISC I-ORG
Pact I-MISC I-ORG
Surgeon O I-ORG
Renat I-PER I-ORG
Akchurin I-PER I-ORG
for I-ORG O
a I-ORG O
Democratic I-ORG I-MISC
Slovakia I-ORG I-MISC
Ottoman O I-MISC
Bank O I-LOC
Jones I-MISC I-PER
Chairman O I-ORG
Alan I-PER I-ORG
Greenspan I-PER I-ORG
Simec I-ORG I-PER
Sidek I-ORG I-MISC
Sidek I-ORG O
Mexican I-MISC I-ORG
ADRs B-MISC I-ORG
Telmex I-ORG O
Televisa I-ORG O
Brazilians I-MISC O
Brazilian I-ORG I-MISC
Plastic I-ORG O
SBCP I-ORG I-LOC
Latin I-LOC I-MISC
America I-LOC O
Hakme I-PER O
Brazilians I-MISC O
SBCP I-ORG O
Vice-President O I-PER
Daily O I-ORG
Quequen B-LOC O
Rosario B-LOC I-ORG
Bahia B-LOC I-ORG
Blanca I-LOC I-ORG
Oats O I-PER
Maize O I-PER
Flint O I-LOC
Maize O I-PER
Dent O I-LOC
Millet O I-PER
Kenda I-MISC I-PER
of I-LOC O
Pacific I-LOC I-ORG
Coast I-LOC I-ORG
Pacific I-LOC I-ORG
Coast I-LOC O
Baja I-LOC I-PER
California I-LOC I-ORG
Baja I-LOC I-ORG
California I-LOC I-ORG
of I-LOC O
Quintana I-LOC I-PER
Roo I-LOC I-PER
SANTIAGO I-PER I-ORG
Finance I-ORG O
Aninat I-PER O
Aninat I-PER O
Congress O I-ORG
Congress O I-ORG
East I-MISC I-LOC
Timorese I-MISC O
Roman B-MISC I-MISC
East I-MISC I-LOC
Timorese-born I-MISC I-LOC
the I-ORG O
Pope O I-PER
Hainan I-LOC O
Wenchang I-LOC O
RANGOON I-LOC I-ORG
( I-ORG O
Rangoon I-ORG I-LOC
) I-ORG O
Insein I-LOC I-MISC
Rangoon I-ORG I-LOC
University I-ORG I-LOC
Vithoon I-PER I-ORG
Amorn I-PER I-ORG
RANGOON I-LOC I-ORG
of I-ORG O
of I-ORG O
Yangon I-ORG I-LOC
San I-PER I-ORG
Suu I-PER I-ORG
Kyi I-PER I-ORG
State I-ORG O
Law I-ORG I-PER
and I-ORG O
Order I-ORG O
SLORC I-ORG I-LOC
National I-ORG I-MISC
League I-ORG I-MISC
for I-ORG O
Democracy I-ORG O
NLD I-ORG I-LOC
San I-PER I-ORG
NLD I-ORG O
Yangon I-LOC O
Union O I-LOC
WTO I-ORG O
ILO I-ORG I-LOC
WTO I-ORG O
International I-ORG I-MISC
Confederation I-ORG I-MISC
of I-ORG O
Trade I-ORG O
ICFTU I-ORG I-LOC
WTO I-ORG O
ILO I-ORG O
Jordan I-PER I-LOC
World I-ORG O
WTO I-ORG O
Hansenne O I-ORG
Jordan I-PER I-LOC
ICFTU I-ORG I-MISC
WTO I-ORG O
Jordan I-PER I-LOC
WTO I-ORG I-MISC
ILO I-ORG I-MISC
Philippines I-LOC I-ORG
ILO I-ORG I-LOC
WTO I-ORG I-MISC
ICFTU I-ORG O
WTO I-ORG O
WTO I-ORG O
K.J. I-PER I-LOC
Matthew I-PER I-LOC
Asia I-MISC I-LOC
Rubber I-MISC O
Markets I-MISC O
meeting I-MISC O
Natural O I-ORG
Note I-PER O
Sakakibara I-PER O
Note I-PER O
Union I-ORG I-LOC
Bank I-ORG I-LOC
of I-ORG O
Switzerland I-ORG I-LOC
Sakakibara I-PER I-LOC
Sakakibara I-PER O
Sakakibara I-PER O
Mr I-PER O
pro-Israeli I-MISC O
Haitham I-ORG I-PER
Haddadin I-ORG I-PER
South I-ORG I-LOC
Lebanon I-ORG I-LOC
Army I-ORG I-LOC
SLA I-ORG I-LOC
SLA I-ORG I-MISC
Lahd I-PER O
Lahd I-PER O
SLA I-ORG O
Lahd I-PER O
SLA I-ORG O
Christian-Shi'ite I-MISC O
Moslem B-MISC I-MISC
Lahd I-PER I-ORG
Lahd I-PER O
pro-Israeli I-MISC O
Guardians I-ORG O
of I-ORG O
the I-ORG O
Okla I-LOC I-PER
AMARILLO I-LOC I-ORG
Slaughter O I-PER
Slaughter O I-PER
Select O I-PER
Choice O I-LOC
Slaughter O I-PER
Select O I-PER
Choice O I-LOC
CATTLE O I-ORG
CALVES O I-ORG
HOGS O I-ORG
NASS I-ORG O
Steer O I-PER
Heifer O I-PER
Cow O I-PER
Bull O I-LOC
Hartford I-LOC I-PER
Conn I-LOC I-PER
BONDS O I-PER
AAA O I-ORG
Jr O I-PER
of I-ORG O
Eugene I-PER I-ORG
Morris I-PER I-ORG
Mills I-PER I-ORG
U.S. I-ORG I-LOC
Circuit O I-ORG
Mills I-PER O
New I-LOC I-ORG
York I-LOC I-ORG
Mana O I-PER
Iowa-S I-LOC I-ORG
Minn B-LOC I-ORG
sales-USDA I-MISC O
Slaughter O I-PER
Select O I-PER
Choice O I-LOC
Select O I-PER
Choice O I-LOC
Carcass O I-ORG
Basis O I-ORG
Thursdays O I-PER
Slaughter O I-PER
Select O I-PER
Choice O I-LOC
Choice O I-ORG
Select O I-PER
Choice O I-LOC
Ago O I-MISC
Ago O I-MISC
Man O I-ORG
Outagmie I-LOC I-ORG
County I-LOC I-ORG
Circuit O I-ORG
Court O I-ORG
Judge O I-ORG
Dennis I-PER I-ORG
Luebke I-PER I-ORG
Luebke O I-PER
Voeks I-PER O
Voeks I-PER O
) O I-ORG
Statistics O I-ORG
Canadian I-ORG I-MISC
Grain I-ORG O
Supplies O I-ORG
Farmers O I-ORG
Deliveries O I-ORG
Curr O I-PER
Wk O I-PER
Ago O I-PER
Curr O I-PER
Wk O I-PER
Date O I-PER
Ago O I-PER
Oats O I-PER
Barley O I-PER
Rye O I-PER
Flax O I-PER
Curr O I-PER
Ago O I-PER
Curr O I-PER
Wk O I-PER
Ago O I-LOC
Oats O I-PER
Barley O I-PER
Rye O I-PER
Flax O I-PER
Canola O I-ORG
Oats O I-PER
Rye O I-PER
Flaxseed O I-PER
Canola O I-PER
Corn O I-PER
Ago O I-MISC
NYMEX I-ORG O
NYMEX I-ORG O
Henry I-LOC I-PER
Hub I-LOC I-PER
Resistance O I-ORG
Gulf I-LOC I-ORG
Coast I-LOC I-ORG
New I-LOC I-ORG
York I-LOC I-ORG
NYMEX I-ORG O
Hub O I-LOC
NYMEX I-ORG O
AECO I-ORG O
NYMEX I-ORG O
Permian I-MISC O
Permian I-MISC I-LOC
West O I-LOC
NYMEX I-ORG O
Southwest O I-ORG
H I-PER I-ORG
McCulloch I-PER I-ORG
ST. I-LOC I-ORG
LOUIS I-LOC I-ORG
St. I-LOC I-ORG
Louis I-LOC I-ORG
Merchants O I-ORG
Exchange O I-ORG
mid-Mississippi I-MISC O
mid-Mississippi I-MISC O
CBOT I-ORG O
CHICAGO I-LOC I-ORG
Trade I-ORG O
Chicago I-LOC I-ORG
St. I-LOC I-ORG
Louis I-LOC I-ORG
Toledo I-LOC I-PER
St. I-LOC I-ORG
Louis I-LOC O
Toledo I-LOC I-PER
Oats O I-PER
Chicago I-LOC I-ORG
St. I-LOC I-ORG
Louis I-LOC I-ORG
Toledo I-LOC I-PER
Action O I-ORG
Performance O I-ORG
Ariz I-LOC I-PER
Motorsport I-ORG I-PER
Traditions I-ORG I-PER
CHICAGO I-LOC I-ORG
Humane O I-ORG
Society O I-ORG
American I-ORG I-MISC
Veterinary I-ORG I-MISC
Rottweilers I-MISC I-PER
shepherds I-MISC O
cocker I-MISC O
spaniels I-MISC O
Dalmatians I-MISC I-ORG
Doberman I-MISC O
Rottweilers I-MISC O
Iowa-S I-LOC I-ORG
Minn B-LOC I-ORG
Nebraska I-LOC O
OMAHA I-LOC I-ORG
Slaughter O I-PER
Last O I-MISC
Sm O I-PER
Pd O I-PER
Wk O I-PER
Sm O I-PER
Pd O I-PER
Basis O I-PER
Delivered O I-PER
Basis O I-PER
Select O I-PER
Choice O I-LOC
Basis O I-PER
Select O I-PER
Choice O I-LOC
Four O I-ORG
Africans I-MISC I-ORG
the I-ORG O
Boutros-Ghali I-PER O
Herri I-ORG I-PER
Batasuna I-ORG I-PER
Fascist O I-MISC
AN I-ORG O
AN I-ORG O
RAI I-LOC O
Mussolini I-PER I-MISC
AN I-ORG O
Mussolini I-PER O
AN I-ORG O
, O I-ORG
AN I-ORG O
Social I-ORG I-MISC
Movement I-ORG I-MISC
MS-Fiamma I-ORG I-LOC
Duce O I-ORG
German I-MISC I-PER
Santa I-PER I-LOC
Claus I-PER I-LOC
Hanover I-LOC O
Milan I-LOC I-ORG
Bharatiya I-ORG I-PER
Janata I-ORG I-PER
Party I-ORG I-PER
BJP I-ORG I-LOC
pro-Hindu I-MISC O
Babri O I-LOC
BJP I-ORG O
Hindu-Moslem I-MISC O
Hindus I-MISC O
Lord O I-LOC
Rama I-PER I-LOC
BJP I-ORG O
Petroleum O I-MISC
CHRISTMAS O I-LOC
Lantau I-MISC I-PER
Peak I-MISC O
Newcastle I-LOC I-ORG
Kaohsiung I-LOC O
China I-ORG I-LOC
Steel I-ORG I-LOC
Royal I-MISC I-ORG
Clipper I-MISC I-ORG
Fos I-LOC O
Coe I-ORG I-PER
and I-ORG O
Clerici I-ORG O
TBN O I-ORG
Dampier I-LOC O
Kaohsiung I-LOC O
China I-ORG I-LOC
Steel I-ORG I-LOC
Conservative I-MISC O
Conservative I-MISC O
Treasuries I-MISC I-ORG
German I-MISC I-PER
Bunds O I-PER
OPEC I-ORG O
OPEC I-ORG O
Saharan I-MISC O
Blend I-MISC I-PER
Minas I-MISC I-PER
Bonny I-MISC I-PER
Light I-MISC I-PER
Arabian I-MISC I-PER
Light I-MISC I-PER
Dubai I-MISC I-LOC
Tia I-MISC I-PER
Juana I-MISC I-PER
Isthmus I-MISC O
Clarke I-PER I-LOC
Major I-PER I-MISC
Exchequer O I-MISC
Major I-PER O
Clarke I-PER I-LOC
Major I-PER I-MISC
Major I-PER I-MISC
STEPHENVILLE I-LOC O
Newfoundland I-LOC I-ORG
Learjet I-MISC I-ORG
36 I-MISC O
Snow I-PER O
Grand I-LOC I-MISC
Rapids I-LOC I-MISC
Shannon I-LOC I-PER
el-Baz I-PER O
Terrorists O I-MISC
Kesers I-PER I-ORG
Karabuluts I-PER I-LOC
Okla I-LOC I-PER
AMARILLO I-LOC I-ORG
Slaughter O I-PER
Holiday O I-MISC
Year O I-MISC
Ago O I-MISC
Date O I-PER
Ago O I-MISC
Slaughter O I-PER
Pen O I-ORG
Select O I-ORG
Choice O I-ORG
Pen O I-ORG
Select O I-ORG
Select O I-PER
Choice O I-LOC
Select O I-PER
Choice O I-LOC
Delphis I-ORG I-PER
Hanover I-ORG O
Delphis I-ORG I-PER
Hanover I-ORG O
A O I-ORG
Baa O I-ORG
ACCESS I-MISC O
NYMEX I-MISC O
ACCESS I-MISC O
Northeastern O I-ORG
NYMEX I-ORG O
ACCESS I-MISC I-LOC
NYMEX I-ORG O
Korydallos I-LOC O
U.S. I-LOC I-MISC
ALBUQUERQUE I-LOC O
N.M. I-LOC O
High I-ORG O
School I-ORG O
New I-ORG I-LOC
Mexico I-ORG I-LOC
Activities I-ORG I-LOC
Association I-ORG I-LOC
Western O I-MISC
Consumer I-PER I-MISC
Project I-PER I-MISC
Ulan I-LOC I-PER
Bator I-LOC I-PER
of I-ORG O
America I-ORG I-LOC
Network I-MISC I-LOC
MCI I-ORG I-MISC
Communications I-ORG I-MISC
Corporation I-ORG I-MISC
Europeans I-MISC I-ORG
Garamba I-LOC I-MISC
Benchaou I-PER O
Moslem B-MISC I-MISC
MANTUA O I-LOC
Mantua O I-LOC
League I-ORG I-MISC
Let I-LOC O
League I-LOC I-MISC
Viva O I-PER
Italia I-LOC I-PER
League I-ORG I-MISC
River O I-LOC
Venice I-LOC O
of I-LOC O
Radiometer O I-ORG
Radiometer I-ORG O
Wednesday I-ORG O
Soeren I-PER I-ORG
Linding I-PER I-ORG
Jakobsen I-PER I-ORG
Antwerp I-ORG I-LOC
Antwerp I-ORG I-LOC
Franc O I-MISC
German I-MISC I-PER
DKV I-ORG O
El I-LOC I-ORG
Salvador I-LOC I-ORG
Hamburg I-LOC I-ORG
Muenchener I-MISC I-ORG
Munich I-ORG I-MISC
of O I-ORG
John I-ORG I-PER
Lewis I-ORG I-PER
UK I-ORG O
Partnership O I-PER
Waitrose I-ORG O
Timah I-ORG O
Receipt O I-PER
Conservative I-MISC O
Cabinet I-ORG O
Newsnight I-MISC O
pro-European I-MISC O
Pro-European I-MISC O
Conservative B-MISC O
MP O I-ORG
Edwina I-PER I-ORG
Currie I-PER I-ORG
Court O I-ORG
Foreign I-ORG O
Affairs I-ORG O
New I-ORG I-LOC
Zealand I-ORG I-LOC
First I-ORG O
and O I-ORG
Lab I-PER O
New I-ORG I-LOC
Zealand I-ORG I-LOC
First I-ORG O
and O I-ORG
NZ I-ORG I-LOC
First I-ORG O
National I-ORG I-MISC
Labour I-ORG I-MISC
and O I-ORG
Canberra I-LOC I-ORG
Bureau O I-ORG
RANGOON I-LOC I-ORG
of I-ORG O
Technology I-ORG O
YIT I-ORG I-LOC
of I-ORG O
Shwe I-LOC I-ORG
Dagon I-LOC I-ORG
State I-ORG O
Law I-ORG I-PER
and I-ORG O
Order I-ORG O
SLORC I-ORG I-LOC
Thai I-MISC I-ORG
Date O I-PER
Arrival O I-ORG
Quantity O I-ORG
Destination O I-ORG
Iran I-MISC I-LOC
Sabr I-MISC I-LOC
Princess I-MISC O
of I-MISC O
Loine I-MISC I-ORG
Deligst I-MISC O
Seagramd I-MISC O
Lucky I-MISC O
Emdldm I-MISC O
Sangthai I-MISC O
Glory I-MISC O
Myos I-MISC I-ORG
Yang I-MISC I-ORG
Budisuryana I-MISC I-ORG
King I-MISC O
Ace I-MISC O
Tong I-MISC I-PER
Shun I-MISC I-PER
Vietnam I-LOC I-MISC
But I-MISC O
Bangkok I-MISC I-LOC
Wen I-ORG I-PER
Hui I-ORG I-PER
Bao I-ORG I-PER
Guilin I-LOC I-MISC
Port O I-ORG
Office O I-ORG
of I-ORG O
China I-ORG I-LOC
General I-ORG O
of I-ORG O
Customs I-ORG I-LOC
Guilin I-LOC O
Sangetsu I-ORG O
Bre-X I-ORG I-PER
Busang I-LOC O
K.T. I-LOC I-PER
Arasu I-LOC I-PER
Busang I-LOC I-MISC
Bre-X I-ORG I-MISC
Bre-X I-ORG I-PER
Mines I-ORG O
and I-ORG O
Secretary-General O I-ORG
Umar I-PER I-ORG
Said I-PER O
Busang I-LOC O
Bre-X I-ORG I-PER
and I-ORG O
Busang I-LOC I-ORG
Bre-X I-ORG O
Bre-X I-ORG O
Bre-X I-ORG O
Busang I-LOC I-PER
Bre-X I-ORG I-LOC
Bre-X I-ORG I-PER
Mines I-ORG O
and I-ORG O
Ministry O I-ORG
Bre-X I-ORG I-PER
Ministry O I-ORG
Bre-X I-ORG I-MISC
Busang I-ORG I-MISC
Busang I-ORG O
Bre-X I-ORG I-PER
PT I-PER I-ORG
Panutan I-PER I-ORG
Duta I-PER I-ORG
Group I-ORG O
Panutan I-PER O
Busang I-ORG O
Group I-ORG O
Honda I-MISC I-ORG
RV I-MISC O
S-MX I-MISC O
S-MX I-MISC O
WTO I-ORG O
World I-ORG I-MISC
Trade I-ORG I-MISC
WTO I-ORG O
I.D.E.A I-ORG O
U.S. I-LOC I-MISC
then-U.S. I-MISC O
Representative O I-ORG
Mickey I-PER I-ORG
Kantor I-PER I-ORG
WTO I-ORG O
WTO I-ORG O
da I-PER O
of I-ORG O
ISEAS I-ORG I-LOC
Policy O I-PER
Round O I-LOC
General I-MISC O
on I-MISC O
Tariffs I-MISC O
and I-MISC O
Trade I-MISC O
GATT I-MISC I-LOC
West O I-LOC
NTT I-ORG I-LOC
and I-ORG O
NTT I-ORG I-LOC
NTT I-ORG I-LOC
NTT I-ORG I-LOC
Posts O I-ORG
and O I-ORG
Telecommunications O I-ORG
NTT I-ORG I-LOC
Ahold I-ORG I-LOC
BILO I-MISC O
BILO I-MISC I-ORG
Kuala I-LOC I-PER
Lumpur I-LOC I-PER
Johor I-LOC I-PER
Bahru I-LOC I-PER
BILO I-MISC O
Ahold I-ORG I-PER
TOPS I-MISC O
Ahold I-ORG O
TOPS I-MISC O
BILO I-MISC O
Ahold I-ORG I-PER
Ahold I-ORG I-PER
Ahold I-ORG I-PER
Lillehammer I-LOC I-MISC
Florence I-PER I-LOC
Masnada I-PER O
ALPINE O I-ORG
SKIING-GLADISHIVA I-MISC I-ORG
Super O I-MISC
TARPON I-LOC I-ORG
SPRINGS I-LOC I-ORG
Florida I-LOC I-ORG
Innisbrook I-LOC I-ORG
Hilton I-LOC I-ORG
Resort I-LOC I-ORG
PGA I-ORG I-MISC
LPGA I-ORG I-MISC
Tours O I-MISC
Tiger I-PER I-ORG
Woods I-PER I-ORG
Renate I-PER O
Goetschl I-PER O
Lillehammer I-LOC I-PER
Norway B-LOC I-ORG
Flachau I-LOC I-PER
1993 I-MISC O
Europa I-MISC I-PER
Cup I-MISC O
Downhill O I-ORG
Markein O I-PER
Masnada I-PER O
Pace I-PER O
Florence I-LOC I-PER
Austria)118 O I-LOC
Super I-MISC I-ORG
G I-MISC O
Nation I-MISC I-ORG
's I-MISC O
Pace I-PER O
Germay O I-LOC
NORDIC O I-ORG
SKIING-WORLD I-MISC I-ORG
CUP I-MISC I-ORG
BIATHLON O I-ORG
Gross I-PER O
Behle I-PER O
ALPINE O I-ORG
SKIING-GOETCHL O I-ORG
BOBSLEIGH-SHIMER I-MISC I-ORG
PILOTS O I-ORG
SURPRISE O I-ORG
USA I-ORG I-LOC
III I-ORG I-LOC
Canada I-ORG I-LOC
I I-ORG O
World I-MISC O
cup I-MISC O
La I-LOC I-ORG
Plagne I-LOC I-ORG
USA I-ORG I-LOC
I I-ORG O
SKIING-CHINESE I-MISC O
Tignes I-LOC O
United I-ORG I-LOC
States I-ORG I-LOC
III I-ORG I-LOC
Italy I-ORG I-LOC
I I-ORG O
Canada I-ORG I-LOC
I I-ORG O
German I-ORG I-MISC
I I-ORG O
Switzerland I-ORG O
I I-ORG O
Germany I-ORG I-LOC
III I-ORG I-LOC
Czech I-ORG I-LOC
Republic I-ORG I-LOC
I I-ORG O
Polomsky I-PER I-ORG
Austria I-ORG I-LOC
I I-ORG O
Britain I-ORG I-LOC
I I-ORG O
United I-ORG I-LOC
States I-ORG I-LOC
I I-ORG O
Hines I-PER I-ORG
Austria I-ORG I-LOC
III I-ORG I-LOC
WOOLMER I-PER O
KANPUR I-LOC O
Kanpur I-LOC O
United I-LOC I-ORG
Province I-LOC I-ORG
Kanpur I-LOC O
India-South I-MISC I-LOC
Africa I-MISC I-LOC
FREESTYLE O I-ORG
SKIING-WORLD I-MISC I-ORG
CUP I-MISC I-ORG
AERIALS O I-ORG
Belarus I-LOC I-ORG
KUUSAMO I-LOC O
TEMBAU I-LOC O
DENPASAR I-LOC O
Bali I-LOC I-PER
Sun I-PER I-ORG
Jun I-PER O
Jaegal I-PER I-ORG
Sung-Yeol I-PER I-ORG
Grunde I-PER I-ORG
Njos I-PER I-ORG
Shimizu I-PER I-ORG
Hiroyasu I-PER I-ORG
Yamakage I-PER O
Xuc I-PER I-ORG
Rulhong I-PER I-ORG
Shimazaki I-PER I-ORG
Kyoko I-PER I-ORG
ALPINE O I-ORG
SKIING-OFFICIALS O I-ORG
HOPE O I-ORG
Whistler I-LOC I-ORG
Mountain I-LOC I-ORG
Rules O I-MISC
PREMIER I-MISC O
DIVISION I-MISC O
premier I-MISC O
ENGLISH I-MISC O
Aston I-ORG I-PER
Villa I-ORG I-PER
Ards I-ORG O
Cliftonville I-ORG O
Glenavon I-ORG O
Linfield I-ORG O
Glenavon I-ORG O
Ards I-ORG O
Cliftonville I-ORG O
Pilkington I-MISC I-PER
Cup I-MISC I-PER
Bath I-ORG O
West I-ORG I-LOC
Hartlepool I-ORG I-LOC
Wasps I-ORG O
Caerphilly I-ORG O
Llanelli I-ORG O
Treorchy I-ORG O
Boroughmuir I-ORG O
Watsonians I-ORG I-PER
Millar I-PER I-MISC
Miller I-PER I-ORG
Rowson I-PER I-ORG
Windass O I-ORG
Olafsson I-PER I-ORG
Hay I-PER O
RETIRING O I-ORG
CAMPESE I-PER I-ORG
WEIGHS O I-ORG
Wallaby I-ORG O
Saracens I-ORG O
New I-ORG I-LOC
South I-ORG I-LOC
Wales I-ORG I-LOC
Super O I-ORG
Wallaby I-ORG I-MISC
Sturridge I-PER I-ORG
Kanchelskis I-PER O
Sheringham I-PER O
Marshall I-PER I-LOC
Wimbledon I-LOC I-ORG
Ekoku I-PER I-ORG
16 O I-ORG
Premier I-MISC O
league I-MISC O
Oxford I-LOC I-ORG
Portsmouth I-LOC I-ORG
VIEIRA I-PER I-ORG
SAVES O I-ORG
ARSENAL I-ORG O
Derby I-ORG I-LOC
Ekoku I-PER O
Wimbledon I-ORG I-LOC
Arsenal I-ORG O
East I-ORG I-LOC
Premier I-MISC O
league I-MISC O
F.A. I-MISC O
Sudbury I-ORG I-LOC
Town I-ORG I-LOC
Ashford I-ORG I-LOC
Town I-ORG I-LOC
CAMPESE I-PER O
WALLABY I-LOC I-MISC
Wallaby I-ORG O
Wallaby I-ORG I-LOC
Full-back O I-LOC
Matthew I-PER I-LOC
Burke I-PER I-LOC
Barbarians I-ORG O
ZIMBABWE I-MISC I-LOC
OPEN I-MISC O
Zimbabwe I-MISC I-LOC
Open I-MISC I-LOC
South I-MISC I-LOC
African I-MISC I-LOC
Murless I-PER O
Fourie I-PER I-ORG
NAMES O I-LOC
N.IRELAND I-LOC O
Albanian I-ORG I-MISC
Football I-ORG I-MISC
Association I-ORG I-MISC
Hafizi I-PER O
Hafizi I-PER O
Belfast I-LOC I-ORG
Sokol I-PER I-ORG
Prenga I-PER I-ORG
JONES I-PER O
Sheffield I-MISC I-ORG
Shield I-MISC I-ORG
Tasmania I-ORG I-LOC
Tasmanian I-MISC O
Pace I-PER O
SHEFFIELD I-MISC I-LOC
SHIELD I-MISC O
SCORE O I-LOC
Sheffield I-MISC I-ORG
Shield I-MISC I-ORG
Tasmania I-ORG I-LOC
Victoria I-ORG I-LOC
Tasmania I-ORG I-LOC
Victoria I-ORG I-LOC
BERTH O I-LOC
ABU I-LOC I-ORG
DHABI I-LOC I-ORG
Do I-PER O
Hwang I-PER I-ORG
Sun I-PER I-ORG
Hong I-PER I-ORG
Koreans I-MISC I-ORG
Koreans I-MISC I-ORG
Widodo I-PER I-ORG
Putra I-PER I-ORG
Sudiriman I-PER O
Do I-PER O
Hwang I-PER I-ORG
Sun I-PER I-ORG
Hong I-PER I-ORG
Maccabi I-ORG O
Lezion I-ORG O
Maccabi I-ORG O
ABU I-LOC I-ORG
DHABI I-LOC I-ORG
Kuwait I-LOC I-ORG
Al-Huwaidi I-PER I-ORG
Indonesia I-LOC I-ORG
Do I-PER O
Hoon I-PER I-ORG
Hwang I-PER I-ORG
Sun I-PER I-ORG
Hong I-PER I-ORG
Putra I-PER I-ORG
UAE I-LOC I-ORG
Kuwait I-LOC I-ORG
National I-ORG I-LOC
EASTERN O I-MISC
CONFERENCE O I-MISC
DIVISION O I-LOC
MIAMI I-ORG I-LOC
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
YORK I-ORG I-LOC
WASHINGTON I-ORG I-LOC
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
JERSEY I-ORG I-LOC
CHICAGO I-ORG I-LOC
CHARLOTTE I-ORG O
WESTERN O I-MISC
CONFERENCE O I-MISC
DENVER I-ORG I-PER
SAN I-ORG I-LOC
ANTONIO I-ORG I-LOC
VANCOUVER I-ORG I-LOC
DIVISION O I-LOC
MIAMI I-ORG I-LOC
VANCOUVER I-ORG I-LOC
DENVER I-LOC I-PER
New I-ORG I-LOC
Jersey I-ORG I-LOC
MIAMI I-ORG I-LOC
Phoenix I-ORG I-PER
SACRAMENTO I-ORG O
Vancouver I-ORG I-LOC
SAN I-ORG I-LOC
ANTONIO I-ORG I-LOC
Charlotte I-ORG I-PER
Indiana I-ORG I-LOC
GOLDEN I-ORG O
STATE I-ORG I-LOC
Orlando I-ORG I-PER
League I-ORG I-MISC
EASTERN O I-MISC
CONFERENCE O I-MISC
T O I-ORG
GF O I-ORG
GA O I-ORG
PTS O I-ORG
OTTAWA I-ORG I-LOC
DIVISION O I-LOC
T O I-ORG
GF O I-ORG
GA O I-ORG
PTS O I-ORG
NEW I-ORG I-LOC
JERSEY I-ORG I-LOC
WASHINGTON I-ORG I-LOC
NY I-ORG O
RANGERS I-ORG O
NY I-ORG O
ISLANDERS I-ORG O
WESTERN O I-MISC
CONFERENCE O I-MISC
CENTRAL O I-MISC
DIVISION O I-MISC
T O I-ORG
GF O I-ORG
GA O I-ORG
PTS O I-ORG
DALLAS I-ORG I-LOC
DIVISION O I-LOC
T O I-ORG
GF O I-ORG
GA O I-ORG
PTS O I-ORG
VANCOUVER I-ORG I-LOC
EDMONTON I-ORG O
SAN I-ORG I-LOC
JOSE I-ORG I-LOC
CALGARY I-ORG I-LOC
CALGARY I-ORG O
WASHINGTON I-ORG I-LOC
OTTAWA I-ORG I-LOC
League I-ORG I-LOC
NY I-ORG O
RANGERS I-ORG O
Philadelphia I-LOC I-ORG
DALLAS I-LOC I-ORG
St I-LOC I-ORG
Louis I-LOC I-ORG
COLORADO I-LOC I-ORG
EDMONTON I-LOC O
Ottawa I-LOC I-ORG
CANUCKS I-ORG O
Vancouver I-ORG I-LOC
Canucks I-ORG I-LOC
Vancouver I-ORG I-LOC
Buffalo I-ORG I-LOC
NHL I-ORG O
Ottawa I-ORG I-LOC
SCHULZ I-PER I-ORG
DEFEATS O I-ORG
RIBALTA I-PER I-ORG
HEAVYWEIGHT O I-ORG
FIGHT O I-ORG
German I-MISC I-PER
International I-ORG I-MISC
Boxing I-ORG I-MISC
Federation I-ORG I-MISC
Suker I-PER O
Mijatovic I-PER I-ORG
BALKAN I-LOC O
REAL I-ORG O
New O I-MISC
Year O I-MISC
Christmas O I-LOC
Suker I-PER O
VOLENDAM I-ORG O
PSV I-ORG O
Tenerife I-ORG O
De I-ORG I-PER
Doetinchem I-ORG I-LOC
The I-ORG O
Rayo I-ORG I-PER
Valencia I-ORG I-LOC
Espanyol I-ORG O
Gijon O I-ORG
Logrones I-ORG O
Compostela I-ORG O
ENGLISHMAN I-MISC O
IRISHMAN I-MISC O
Charlton I-PER I-ORG
Charlton I-PER I-ORG
Charlton I-PER I-ORG
1966 I-MISC O
